<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Hollomby</title>
    <link>https://alexdata1.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alex Hollomby</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>me@example.com (sharadcodes)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>me@example.com (sharadcodes)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2021 Janne Kemppainen All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexdata1.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Case Study - Cyclistic</title>
      <link>https://alexdata1.github.io/2022/06/01/cyclistic_markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>me@example.com (sharadcodes)</author>
      <guid>https://alexdata1.github.io/2022/06/01/cyclistic_markdown/</guid>
      <description>Notes on the project Here is a link to my GitHub repository for this project, which includes this markdown document along with the code used in the project.
The Tableau Public page for this project contains all visualisations I created as part of this project (these are also shown in Step 6 of the markdown).
Introduction As the culmination of my study of Google&amp;rsquo;s Data Analytics Professional Certificate, I carried out a case study as a capstone project to showcase the technical abilities that I learned on the course, as well as my understanding of the data analysis process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://alexdata1.github.io/2022/05/31/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>me@example.com (sharadcodes)</author>
      <guid>https://alexdata1.github.io/2022/05/31/cv/</guid>
      <description>Alex Hollomby Profile Versatile individual looking to begin a career in data analytics. Thorough understanding of the data analysis process and strong technical proficiency in a variety of tools used for analysis, including Excel, R, SQL, and Tableau.
Experienced in understanding stakeholder requirements, processing and cleaning data, creating visualisations and presenting findings. Recognised as able to work effectively both independently and as part of a team.
Having completed the Google Data Analytics Certificate, carried out a case study that can be viewed on my personal portfolio at alexdata1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
